<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Paper Cup Construction</title><link>https://papercupconstruction.com/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Paper Cup Construction</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://papercupconstruction.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://papercupconstruction.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://papercupconstruction.com/about/</guid><description>Why Paper Cup Construction? Playing with simple constructive toys has been correlated with improved visual-spatial reasoning, mathematical and problem solving abilities, language acquisition, social skills, and creativity. Paper cups strike a superb balance between artistic expression and structural, analytical thinking. In addition, they facilitate the development of fine and gross motor skills, patience for building large structures, and persistence in the face of engineering difficulties. Paper cup construction also promotes significant collaborative behavior while builders work together to make especially large towers or combine individual constructions into elaborate villages.</description></item><item><title>Book</title><link>https://papercupconstruction.com/book/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://papercupconstruction.com/book/</guid><description>Book Fundamentals of Paper Cup Construction explores the many wonderful qualities of paper cups and some of the fundamental techniques of the amazing art and science paper cup construction. The book includes a comprehensive glossary of paper cup construction terminology as well as a gallery of construction ideas. It also offers tips for organizing your own paper cup construction activities for small or large groups. The techniques described in the book only scratch the surface of the many amazing structures you can build with paper cups.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://papercupconstruction.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://papercupconstruction.com/contact/</guid><description>Contact Have a question or comment?
Interested in researching paper cup construction in educational psychology?
Want to share your favorite photos in our featured gallery?
Reach out to us at: contact@PaperCupConstruction.com</description></item><item><title>Gallery</title><link>https://papercupconstruction.com/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://papercupconstruction.com/gallery/</guid><description>Gallery</description></item></channel></rss>